jott.com 2017-09-17

# Privacy Policy | Juxta Labs

JUXTA LABS PRIVACY POLICY

  Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to the websites, mobile applications, and other online products

and services (the “Services”) operated by Juxta Labs Inc., its subsidiaries, and other affiliates

(“Juxta,” “we,” “us,” and “our”). This does not apply to personal information collected offline.

This Privacy Policy also explains the choices you have about the way your personal information

is collected and used.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully because by registering for or using the Services, you agree to be

bound to this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into our Services Terms of Use, available here, <http://www.juxtalabs.com/terms-of-service/>.

We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to keep up to date

on how we are handling your personal information.

#### **Types of Personal Information We Collect**

When you use our Services, we may collect your personal information. The types of personal

information we collect from you depends on the services and the features you use on the Services.

Personal information refers to information that directly identifies, or can be used to determine the

identity of, a person. This information may include:

**Registration, Profile, and Device Identification Information**. We may collect information from you

when you register directly with us or through a third-party Social Networking Software (“SNS”)

such as Facebook. That information may include, among other things, your full name, email

addresses, age, birthday, password, phone numbers, schools attended or attending, device

identifiers, and other information you provide. We may also collect information from your user

profile, including, among other information: photos, usernames, gender, geographic information,

likes, interests, bio, country, character names, email addresses, and contact information for and

links to other websites. Depending on how you access our Services, we may also collect device

identification information, including MAC address and IP address. If you choose to connect your

mobile device contacts or address book with our Services, we will collect, synchronize and store

your contacts or address book information. We may collect the phone numbers and names of your

contacts enable you and your contacts to connect and use our Services.

**  Payment Information**. If you purchase a license to use virtual currency and assets, we will collect

the billing and financial information necessary to process the fee for those virtual items. That

information may include your payment card details and postal and email addresses.

**Information About You From an SNS.** When you use the Services in conjunction with an SNS such

as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, or Google, you allow us to access information from your profile

on the SNS. The information you allow us to access varies by SNS and the privacy settings you and

your friends establish at the SNS. You should refer to the applicable SNS for more information

about their privacy settings. Depending on your SNS privacy settings, we may access and store

some or all of the following information: your public data, full name, your profile picture or its

URL, your user ID number, the user ID numbers and other public data for your friends, the login

email address you provided to the SNS, your geographic location, your gender, and your birthday.

By accessing or using one of our Services, you authorize us to collect, store, and use any and all

information that you agreed the SNS could provide to us through the SNS Application

Programming Interface (“API”).

**Customer Support Information.** We will collect and store the contact information you provide to our

customer support personnel, information about your use of our Services, and your user ID number.

We will also store the communications you have with us and any information contained in those

communications.

**SMS Notifications and Similar Notifications.** We may collect and store the information you

provide, including your telephone number, when you sign up to have SMS notifications sent

directly to your mobile phone.

**Technical and Usage Information.** When you access our Services,

we collect information about your mobile device or computer system, including MAC address, IP

address and mobile device ID. We also collect usage statistics about your interactions with the

Services. This information is typically collected through the use of server log files or web log files

(“Log Files”), mobile device software development kits and tracking technologies like browser

cookies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information. Some of the cookies the

Services place on your computer are linked to your user ID number.

#### **How We Collect Information**

We collect information in various ways, including the following:

Information Collected Directly From You and Other Users. When you use one of our

applications, we collect and store certain information that you provide directly, through an SNS, or

through a third party. We also collect information about your use of the Services and your interaction with

other users.

**Cookies and Similar Collection Methods.** We also collect technical information about your usage of

the Services, and we use various technologies to collect information about cookies, IP addresses,

device type, device identifiers, browser types, browser language, pages accessed, URLs, platform

type, the clicks, domain names, landing pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages,

application state and the date and time of activity with our applications, and other similar

information. We may associate this information with your user ID number for our internal use. We

may also employ other technologies including web beacons and tracking pixels. If you so desire,

you can adjust settings on your web browser to limit the type of cookies allowed, but note that these

settings may not apply to supercookies and other pervasive tracking technologies. Please note that

companies delivering advertisements in our applications or on our websites may also use cookies or

other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies.

**Communications Features**. You may be able to take part in certain activities on our Services that

allow you to communicate and share information with us and other users of our Services. These

include participating in forums and message boards, posting comments to other users’ profiles or

boards, sending private or group messages or invitations, chatting with other users, and posting

photos, videos and other files. We may record and store archives of these communications on our

servers. You acknowledge and consent to the recording and storage of these communications.

 Other Sources. We may collect or receive information from other sources including (i) other Juxta

users who choose to upload their mobile device contacts and (ii) third party information providers.

This information may be used to supplement your profile and it will be combined with other

information we collect.

#### **How We Use the Information We Collect**

We use your information primarily as necessary to provide you with the Services, including in one or

more of the following ways:

**Service Support and Improvement.** We may use your personal information to create your account,

allow use of our Services, suggest and make connections with other users, enable user-to- user

communications, provide technical support and respond to user inquiries, and analyze what our

users prefer, so that we can design better products and services. We may analyze the information

that is collected with cookies and other tracking technologies to help us improve our function and to

modify the services and information that we provide.

**Communications.** We also use your information to communicate with you about your inquiries, our

company, and related news, as well as to send you promotional emails, surveys, newsletters, or

notifications. If you have provided your email address or phone number to us, we may use it to

respond to (i) customer support inquiries, and (ii) keep you informed of your activity, including

comments from friends, notifications about application status. Additionally, if you have chosen to

synchronize your mobile device contacts with our Services, your decision may initiate SMS

notifications directly to your friends to invite them to our Services and alert them to relevant

application activity. To invite your friends to join you in using our applications and other Services,

the messages sent to your friends may include your name, school network and profile photo. We

may send promotional email messages and SMS messages directly or in partnership with parties

other than Juxta. These messages notify you of application activity, provide application updates and

other relevant information and may allow you to use the applicable application on your phone. The

sending of SMS notifications may be handled through a third party service provider.

With your consent, we may send push notifications to your mobile device to provide application

updates and other relevant messages. You may be able to manage push notifications from the

applicable application or from your device’s settings. Some of our Services have direct messaging

features built in (In-Band Messages). When available, we may send In-Band Messages directly to

your mobile device to notify you of application activity, advertisements, offers and other relevant

communication.

**Fraud Prevention and Legal Compliance.** We may use your information to prevent fraud or

potentially illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service.

**Customized User Experiences.** We may use your personal information to create customized

experiences, or to provide you information or services tailored to your interests and preferences.

We may use your IP address and other similar information to make our Services easier to use and

navigate as well as to personalize the content provided on the Services.

**Product Improvement:** If you choose to download our apps, subscribe to our products, participate in

our online services, or to register for other Juxta products or services, we will collect the

information that you disclose and analyze the data to discover new facts that could help us better

understand our products and services. We may use this information for our internal business

purposes, such as research to improve our products and analyses that may help us better market our

products.

**Advertising, Marketing, and Promotions:** We may use your information for generating web

analytics to compile user information for marketing purposes, advertising, conducting marketing

analysis, providing you with recommendations for products or services based on your profile, and

promotional material planning and distribution. In particular, we may use your information to

deliver and target advertising, to notify users of application updates, to provide application leader

boards and promote application user achievements, to solicit input and feedback to improve our

products and services, and to inform users about new products or promotional offers.

#### **Sharing Your Information**

We may share your personal information, with third parties in the following circumstances:

Some of your profile information may be exposed publicly when you participate in the Services such as

by posting content, chatting with other users, or commenting on content. This includes: your name,

profile photos, username, school or network name, bio and descriptions of your activity.

Your information and your online communications may be accessed and monitored as necessary to

provide the Services and may be disclosed or reported: (i) if we have a good faith belief that we are

required to disclose the information by law, (ii) in response to legal process (for example, a court order,

search warrant or subpoena); (ii) to satisfy applicable laws, (iii) if we believe that the Services are being

used to commit a crime, (iii) including, but not limited to, to report such criminal activity or to

exchange information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and

credit risk reduction, (iv) if we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to

the health or safety of a person or the general public, and (v) in order to protect the rights or property of

Juxta, including to enforce our Terms of Service.

If you give us your consent, we may actively share personal information with third party advertisers for

their direct marketing purposes. We may share aggregated or anonymous information and certain

technical information to develop and deliver targeted advertising in the Services and on the websites of

third parties. We may also allow advertisers to collect those types of information within the Services

and they may share it with us. We may use this information for behavioral advertising and for web

analytics. Our collection, use, and disclosure of anonymous or aggregated information are not subject to

any of the restrictions in this privacy policy.

We may display an “offer wall” that is hosted by an offer wall provider. The offer wall allows third

party advertisers to provide virtual currency to users in exchange for interacting with an advertisement

or for completing a marketing offer that may include signing up for an account with one of those

advertisers. These are not offers made by us. We may display these offers to you based on certain

information, such as your geographic area or anonymous demographic information. If you click on one

of these advertisements, you will no longer be on a site hosted by Juxta or a partnering SNS.

We may provide your information to third party companies to perform services on our behalf, including

payment processing, data analysis, message delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing.

If we sell all or a portion of our business, we may transfer all of your information, including personal

information, to the successor organization.

#### **Security of Your Information**

We implement security measures we believe are reasonable to protect your information. It is

important that you protect and maintain the security of your account and you need to immediately

notify us of any unauthorized use of your account. No website, mobile application or Internet

transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data

loss, or other breaches or other type of misuse will never occur. We may post a notice via the Services

if a security breach occurs. We may also send you notice by the contact information you have

provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to

receive written notice of a data privacy or security breach. If you have reason to believe that your

personal information that we have collected or our Services’ security has been breached, please notify

us by [support@juxtalabs.com.](http://support@juxtalabs.com./)

#### **Accessing and Controlling Your Information**

If you have accounts on our Services you can access and edit the information you provided to us

through individual settings in the Services. If you want to delete your accounts and information on our

Services, please contact us directly at: [support@juxtalabs.com.](http://support@juxtalabs.com./). To manage the information we receive

about you from an SNS you will need to follow the instructions at that the SNS. Once we receive your

information from an SNS, that information is stored and used by us in accordance with this Privacy

Policy.

**Opting Out of Marketing Communications**

Similarly, you may opt-out of commercial communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in an

email or by replying “STOP” to text messages. We will process your requests as soon as possible, but

please be aware that it may take us some time to respond to your request and, in some circumstances

regarding opt-out requests, you may receive a few more messages until your request is processed.

#### **Our Policy Toward Children**

Our Services are not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any

personal information from such children. Children under the age of 13 should not use our Services at

any time. If we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child under the

age of 13 we will delete such information as quickly as possible.

#### **International Operations and Information Transfer**

We may transfer data to foreign affiliates, partners or vendors. If you are located outside of the United

States of America and choose to use our Services and share information with us, we may transfer your

data across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to the United States or other countries or

jurisdictions around the world, and process it there. If you are visiting from Canada, the European

Union, or other jurisdictions with laws governing data protection that may differ from United States

law, please note that you are transferring your personal information to the United States which does not

have the same data protection laws as your country and which may provide more limited recourse

mechanisms, including dissimilar or, at times, weaker data protection rights. With knowledge of these

risks, by providing your personal information you consent to: (1) the use of your personal information

for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and (2) the transfer of your

personal information to the United States and other countries as indicated above.

#### **Third Party Apps and Websites**

Our Services may link to third-party apps and websites from companies other than Juxta that may link

to their own websites, such as offer wall providers. We are not responsible for the privacy practices,

security, or the content of such websites. If you have any questions about how these other websites use

your information, you should review their policies and contact them directly. We are not responsible for

the actions of third-party advertisers and service providers.

#### **Third Party Advertisers**

We may use advertisers, third party ad networks, and other advertising companies to serve

advertisements on the Services. Please be advised that such advertising companies may gather

information about your visit to the Services or other websites (such as through cookies, web beacons,

and other technologies) to enable such advertising companies to market products or services to you, to

monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which webpages you were viewing when such

ads were delivered. If you would like to learn more about this practice, and know your choices with

respect to it, [please visit here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

AGAIN, PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT COVER THE COLLECTION

AND USE OF INFORMATION BY SUCH THIRD PARTY SITES AND ADVERTISERS.

#### **Assignment**

In the event that all or part of our assets are sold or acquired by another party, or in the event of a

merger, you grant us the right to assign your personal information collected via the Services.

#### **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to our Privacy

Policy, we will notify you and other users by posting the changes on the Juxta Labs Services or by

using the contact information you have on file with us and will indicate when such changes will become

effective. By continuing to use our Services you are agreeing to be bound by any changes or revisions

made to this Privacy Policy.

#### **California Privacy Rights &amp; How We Respond to Do-Not- Track Disclosures**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to the Services who are California residents to

request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their

direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the address provided at the

bottom of this Privacy Policy.

We do not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you

affirmatively agree to such disclosure, typically by “opting in” to receive information from a third party

that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our Services. If you do ask us to

share your personal information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share

information in connection with that specific promotion, as we do not share information with any third

party (other than our service providers) on a continual basis.

At this time our Services do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms,

which may include ‘do not track’ instructions.

#### **Agreement to Arbitrate**

By visiting the Services or otherwise using the Services, you and we agree that, if there is any

controversy, claim, action or dispute arising out of or related to any transaction conducted on the

Services, or the breach, enforcement, interpretation, or validity of the Privacy Policy or any part of them

(collectively, a &quot;Dispute&quot;), both parties shall first try in good faith to settle such Dispute by providing

written notice to the other party describing the facts and circumstances of the Dispute and allowing the

receiving party thirty (30) days in which to respond to or settle the Dispute.

Notice shall be sent:

To Juxta Labs Inc., 525 Brannan St. Suite 408, San Francisco, CA 94107,

ATTN: Legal Department, or

To you at: your contact information that we have on file.

Both you and we agree that this dispute resolution procedure is a condition precedent that must be

satisfied before initiating any litigation or filing any claim against the other party.

IF ANY DISPUTE CANNOT BE RESOLVED BY THE ABOVE DISPUTE RESOLUTION PROCEDURE, YOU AGREE

THAT THE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION FOR SUCH DISPUTE WILL BE DECIDED BY BINDING

ARBITRATION ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS. ARBITRATION ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS MEANS THAT YOU

WILL NOT HAVE, AND YOU WAIVE, THE RIGHT FOR A JUDGE OR JURY TO DECIDE YOUR CLAIMS, AND

THAT YOU MAY NOT PROCEED IN A CLASS, CONSOLIDATED OR REPRESENTATIVE CAPACITY. Other rights

that you and we would have in court will not be available or will be more limited in arbitration, including

discovery and appeal rights. All such Disputes shall be determined by arbitration in the San Francisco,

CA area, exclusively submitted to JAMS (www.jamsadr.com) for binding arbitration under its rules then

in effect, before one arbitrator to be mutually agreed upon by both parties.

The arbitrator, and not any federal, state or local court or agency, shall have exclusive authority to resolve

any dispute arising under or relating to the interpretation, applicability, enforceability or formation of

the Privacy Policy, including any claim that all or any part of the Privacy Policy is void or voidable.

#### **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please

send an email to [support@juxtalabs.com](mailto:support@juxtalabs.com) or write to use at the following address:

Juxta Labs Inc.

525 Brannan St. Suite 408

San Francisco, CA 94107

Effective: 03/15/2017

___________________________________________
